咖啡
Coffee.
-谢谢 -卡布其诺 -谢谢（意大利语）
-Thank you. -Cappuccino. -Grazie
莫妮卡的热苹果汁
And a nice,hot cider for Monica.
谢谢
Thank you.
瑞秋,为何我的肉桂棒上有橡皮擦?
Rach,why does my cinnamon stick have an eraser?
这就是原因,
That's why.
对不起
Sorry.
六人行 第1季 第15集 吸大麻的家伙
The One With The Stoned Guy
钱德
Chandler?
泰洛克小姐,你今天真漂亮
Miss Tedlock,you look lovely today.
我能说这件衣服真好看吗?
That is a very flattering sleeve length on you.
科斯特.力克先生希望你在下班后 能到他办公室去
Mr. Costilick would like you to stop by his office today.
如果他是为搞笑备忘录 不是我干的,
If it's about those prank memos,I wasn't involved.
和我完全没有关系.真的.
Nothing at all. Really.
弗兰克,办公室里没有地方容纳这些恶作剧.
And frankly,those shenanigans have no place in an office environment.
各位,
Hey,you guys!
钱德说他有天大的好消息
Chandler's coming and he has incredible news.
所以他来的时候我们就……
So when he gets here,let's all act,like,you know
不管了,这一定很有意思.
Never mind. But it was gonna be really good.
到底怎么了…
What's going on?
今天和平常没什么两样
So it's a typical day at work...
然后艾尔叫我到他办公室 说他要我当电脑处理的主管
...and Big Al tells me he wants to make me processing supervisor.
-真是太好了 -恭喜...
-That is great! -Congratulations!
所以我就辞职不干了
So I quit.
为什么?
Why?
为什么?因为这只是暂时的工作
Why? This was a temp job.
钱德,你已在公司五年了
Chandler,you've been there for five years.
我知道,但接受升职 不就承认这就是我的目的
I know,but if I took it,I'd be admitting that this is what I do.
这是不是意味着我们必须开始自己购买卫生纸？
Does that mean we have to start buying our own toilet paper?
那是有大照片的乔伊，丹?
That was Joey Tribbiani with the big picture. Dan?
那不是能赚更多钱?
Was it more money?
我不在乎,我不想成为 坐在办公室到午夜
Doesn't matter. I just don't want to be a guy who sits in his office...
担心"WEENUS"的人
...worrying about the WENUS.
"WENUS"?
The "WENUS"?
"每周估计净值使用系统" 这是电脑处理的术语
Weekly estimated net usage system. It's a processing term.
哦，那个"WENUS"啊
Oh,that WENUS.
你有何打算?
What will you do?
我也不知道该怎么办 我只知道我不会再待在那儿工作了
I don't know. But I won't figure it out working there.
我有一份你可以做的工作
I have something you can do!
我的新按摩客户史提夫
I have this new massage client,Steve.
他开了一家餐厅
Anyway,he's opening up a restaurant...
他正在寻找总厨师
...and he's looking for a head chef.
-你好 -你好.
-Hi,there. -Hi.
我知道你是个厨师,而且我先想到你
I know. You're a chef and I thought of you first.
但钱德目前没有工作所以...
But Chandler's the one who needs a job right now,so....
我没有太多厨师的经验
I just don't have a lot of chef-ing experience.
除非那是一家只卖烤面包片的餐厅
Unless it's an all-toast restaurant.
他想要什么菜色?
What is he looking for?
他想要菜色丰富多变
He wants to do something eclectic.
因此他在找一个能创造出整个菜单的人
He's looking for someone who can create the entire menu.
意下如何?
So,what do you think?
谢了.我大概没资格戴白色大帽吧
Thanks. I just don't see myself in a big,white hat.
莫妮卡,知道吗?
Oh,Monica! Guess what?
一个完美的助跑,然后就自然而然出现了,完美的
a perfect run-up and there he goes,a perfect....
看看这个
Watch stuff like this...
你就知道为什么变革仅仅是理论上的事情了.
...and you realize why evolution is just a theory.
你能透过衬衫看见我的乳头吗?
Can you see my nipples through this shirt?
看不见,但别担心,它们还在
No,but don't worry. I'm sure they're still there.
你要上哪儿去,西装笔挺先生?
Where are you going?
我和罗伯提曼博士有约,求职顾问阿哥哥
I have an appointment with Dr. Robert Pilman,career counselor-a-go-go!
-阿哥哥是我加的 -求职顾问?
-I added the "a-go-go." -Career counselor?
你们都已找到人生的方向
You guys all know what you want to do.
还没
I don't.
在客厅里的各位 全都都已找到人生的方向
You guys in the living room all know what you want to do.
你们有目标,有梦想,但我却没有梦想
You have goals. You have dreams. I don't have a dream!
少见的“我没有梦想”演说
The lesser-known "I Don't Have a Dream" speech.
我爱我的人生!我爱我的人生!
I love my life! I love my life!
布莱恩的歌
"Brian's Song"!
-见面的结果如何? -相当顺利
-The meeting went great? -So great!
他告诉我未来餐厅的位置
He showed me where the restaurant's gonna be.
就在第十街不太大也不太小,大小适中
It's not too big or too small. It's just right.
前任老板是金发女人和几只熊吗?
Was it formerly owned by a blond woman and some bears?
周一我们要煮一餐让他品尝 有点像是面试
I'm cooking for him Monday,kind of an audition.
菲比,他也要你在场 这样对我有好处 因为你可以发出好吃的赞叹声
Phoebe,he wants you here. It's great. You can make yummy noises.
-你打算做什么? -好吃的声音.
-What are you gonna make? -Yummy noises.
莫妮卡,你要做什么菜? 我也不知道,但一定会很棒的
-And Monica,what are you gonna make? -I don't know. It's gotta be great.
我知道你可以做什么了!
I know what you can make! I know!
你应该用那些东西做这个.
You should make that thing with the stuff.
你知道用那些东西做的这个?
You know that thing with the stuff?
好吧,我也不知道
Okay,I don't know.
各位,谁知道附近有约会的绝佳地点?
Anyone know a good date place in the neighborhood?
东尼餐厅如何?吃下32盎斯的牛排就免费
How about Tony's? If you finish a 32-ounce steak,it's free.
谁知道和美洲豹约会,哪儿是好地点?
Anyone know a good place if you're not dating a puma?
-你要和谁约会? -是昆虫女?
-Who are you going out with? -ls this the bug lady?
我爱你,罗斯
"I love you,Ross."
她叫希莉亚,不是昆虫女 她是昆虫博物馆的主任
Her name is Celia and she's insect curator at the museum.
-你们打算如何共渡? -出去吃晚餐
-What are you gonna do? -Go out to dinner...
然后带她回我的住处 介绍我的猴子给她认识
...then bring her back to my place and introduce her to my monkey.
他没用比喻
And he's not speaking metaphorically.
回你的住处?你想...
So back to your place? You thinking maybe....
我不知道…
Well,I don't know....
我希望…
I'm hoping....
告诉你,那猴子是魅力十足
That monkey is a chick magnet.
她看见它那毛绒绒可爱的小脸 然后一切就搞定
She'll take one look at his cute,little face and it'll seal the deal.
希莉亚,别担心,它不会伤害你的
Celia,don't worry. He's not gonna hurt you!
用安抚的语调
Soothing tones.
-过来,马修 -我受不了了.
-Here,Marcel. -I can't stand this.
-它的爪子在我的 -乖..
-He's got his claws on my -Yeah,all right.
试试这鲑鱼慕斯
Okay,try this salmon mousse.
好吃
Good.
比其他的鲑鱼慕斯好吃?
Is it better than the other salmon mousse?
-更滑更柔 -是吗?这样更好?
-It's creamier. -Yeah? Well,is that better?
我不知道.我们在谈一条搅成泡沫的鱼
I don't know. We're talking about whipped fish.
我能不吐出来就已经不错了
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
天啊,你怎么了?
God,what happened to you?
8个半小时的天资测验
Eight and a half hours of aptitude tests...
智力测验,个性测验,我了解了什么?
...intelligence tests,personality tests,and what do I learn?
你适合在大型跨国公司 资料处理部门方面发展
"You're suited for data processing for a large multinational corporation."
这太好了 因为你已知道该如何做
That's so great! You already know how to do that.
你们能相信吗?
Can you believe it?
我不像是做那种酷工作的人吗?
Don't I seem like I should be doing something cool?
我总是想像自己能做点事情
I just always pictured myself doing something....
事情!
Something!
钱德,我知道
Chandler,I know,I know.
嗨,你可以透过你的衬衫 看自己的乳头
Hey,you can see your nipples through this shirt.
这个或许能让你开心点
Maybe this will cheer you up.
5小时前我吃了一颗葡萄 所以我最好该和你平分
I had a grape about five hours ago,so I better split this with you.
它本来就应该那么小 这是餐前开胃菜
It's supposed to be small. It's a pre-appetizer.
法国人称它为“阿姆兹布许”
The French call it an amuse-bouche.
这简直是太神奇了
Well,it is amusing.
温蒂,对,八点
Hi,Wendy. Yeah,8:00.
我们不是说过吗?每小时十块
What did we say,$10 an hour?
很好,再见了
Okay,great. All right,I'll see you then.
-什么每小时十块? -我请餐厅里的女服务生帮忙
-$10 an hour for what? -A waitress from work is helping me.
服务生?
Waitressing?
当然我考虑过你.但...
Of course I thought of you. But....
-但是… -但是什么?
-But.... -But,but....
但是今晚一定要做到完美,你知道吗?
But it's just this night has to go just perfect,you know?
温蒂的经验丰富,是个职业服务生
Wendy's more of a professional waitress.
我应该继续保持业余的姿态 将来才能在奥运会上当服务生
And I'm maintaining my amateur status so I can waitress in the Olympics.
我不想自吹自擂 但我在76年的因斯布鲁克当过服务生
I don't mean to brag,but I waited tables at lnnsbruck in '76.
带回家一块铜牌.
Took home a bronze.
阿姆兹-布许?
Amuse-bouche?
和我说话
Talk to me.
早上我坐地铁时 发生了一件诡异的事
A weird thing happened on the train this morning
说猥亵的话
Talk dirty.
-这里? -对.
-Here? -Come on. Come on.
说点火辣的
Say something hot.
什么?什么?
What? What?
外阴.
Vulva.
外阴?
Vulva?
我当时好害怕,她吓了我一跳
I panicked,all right? She took me by surprise.
但并未完全失去自我.我们以爱抚收场
But it wasn't a total loss. We ended up cuddling.
爱抚?几次?
You cuddled? How many times?
闭嘴,那种感觉好好
Shut up. It was nice.
我不是那种讲猥亵话的人
I don't think I'm a dirty-talking kind of guy.
你只要说出你想对她如何 或是你想她对你如何
Just say what you wanna do to her. Or what you want her to do to you.
或是别人想对彼此如何
Or what other people might be doing to each other.
这样吧,对我说吧
I'll tell you what. Try something on me.
开什么玩笑
Please be kidding.
有何不可,
Why not?
只要闭上眼睛告诉我 现在你想干什么
Just close your eyes and tell me what you'd like to be doing right now.
好吧…我在我的住处
I'm in my apartment....
-然后呢? -你不在那里.
-Yeah,what else? -You're not there.
-我们在进行这样的谈话 -好的,我要开始了,准备好了吗?
-We're not having this conversation. -All right,I'll start. Ready?
噢,罗斯
Oh,Ross...
你让我欲火焚身,我要你舔我
...you get me so hot. I want your lips on me now.
-该你了 -我看还是算了吧
-Now you say something. -I really don't think so.
你喜欢她吧?想再见到她吗?
You like this woman,right? You wanna see her again,right?
如果你无法对我说出猥亵的话 你如何对她说呢?
If you can't talk dirty to me,how will you talk dirty to her?
现在告诉我你想爱抚我的屁股
Now tell me you wanna caress my butt!
好吧,转过去
Okay,turn around.
我不想你盯着我看
I don't want you staring at me.
好吧,我不看,说吧
All right,I'm not looking. Go ahead.
我要...
I want Okay,I want...
用我的双唇感觉你那光滑的皮肤
...to feel your hot,soft skin with my lips.
这就对了,继续
There you go. IKeep going,keep going.
我要用我的舌头…
I want to take my tongue and
快说啊
Say it.
快说
Say it!
舔遍你的全身
run it all over your body...
直到你颤抖…
... until you're trembling with
然后呢?
With?
-真好笑 -你不会相信的
-Funny story. -You're not gonna believe this.
我一向赞成你们两个小子交往
I was always rooting for you two kids to get together.
-颤抖那一段不错 -闭嘴!
-The trembling thing was nice. -Shut up!
你睡觉时以前的公司又打电话来
That guy from your old job called again.
-又打来? -一遍又一遍.
-Again? -And again and again and again.
又打来了
And again.
嘿，科斯特林克先生,15楼的情况如何?
Hey,Mr. Costilick. How's life on the 1 5th floor?
我也想念你.
Yeah,I miss you too.
对,偷自己家里的笔不够刺激
It's a lot less satisfying to steal pens from your own home.
你真慷慨,但这不是钱的问题
That's very generous. But this isn't about the money.
我需要的不只是一份工作 我要的是我真正想要的
I need more than a job. I need something I really care ab
这是你稍早提过的年终红利之外的津贴?
That's on top of the year-end bonus?
你的梦想…
Your dream!
艾尔,我不是在故意为难你
Look,Al,I'm not playing hardball here,okay?
这不是交涉,这叫拒绝
This is not a negotiation. This is a rejection!
不,别再讲数字了
Stop saying numbers!
告诉你,你看错人了，你看错人了
I'm telling you,you've got the wrong guy!
星期一见
I'll see you Monday!
好大,比小格子大多了
Wow! It's huge! It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
这是一个格间!
This is a cube!
看这里.
Look at this.
你有窗户!
You have a window!
没错,还有美丽的风…
Yes,indeed-y. With a beautiful view of
看,有人在小便
Look! That guy's peeing!
风景看够了,看这个
That's enough of the view. Check this out.
坐下
Okay,sit down here.
这个最酷,
This is great.
-准备好没? -好了
-You ready? -Yeah.
海伦,能进来一下吗?
Helen,could you come in here?
谢谢你,海伦,没事了
Thank you,Helen. That'll be all.
最后一次了,我保证
Last time I do that. I promise.
-她看起来不怎么热情 -我知道.她没有个性.
-She doesn't seem very warm. -I know. She has no personality.
温蒂,不要这样对我.
Wendy,don't do this to me.
我们约好的.你答应过我
We had a deal. Yeah,you promised.
-那是谁? -叛徒温蒂
-Who was that? -Wendy bailed.
我没服务生了
I have no waitress.
真是太糟糕了.再见
That's too bad. Bye-bye.
一小时十元!一小时十二元!
Ten dollars an hour! Twelve dollars an hour!
我希望可以 但我已经计划好去走走
I wish I could,but I've made plans to walk around.
你逃婚之后我一直关心你
When you ran out on your wedding,I was there.
我让你有地方住 如果这样对你仍毫无意义…
I put a roof over your head! If that means nothing....
一小时二十元
Twenty dollars an hour.
成交
Done.
欢迎光临莫妮卡家 我能帮你拿外套吗?
Hello. Welcome to Monica's. May I take your coat?
（喜剧演员 强・洛维兹）
Jon Lovitz
-史提夫 -莫妮卡
-Hi,Steve. -Hello,Monica.
招待小姐
Hello,greeter girl.
-她叫瑞秋 -好的,
-This is Rachel. -Yeah,okay.
味道好香
Everything smells so delicious.
我早已忘记这种美味的…
I can't remember ever smelling such a delicious combination of
香味
Okay,smells.
-这房子真漂亮 -谢谢,想参观一下吗?
-It's a lovely apartment. -Thank you. Would you like a tour?
我只是客套一下,但,好吧
I was just being polite,but all right.
-怎么了? -他坐计程车来时
-What's up? -ln the cab on the way over...
燃了一根草
...Steve blazed up a doobie.
什么?
What?
抽了一根大麻… 好了,我懂
Smoked a joint,you know? Lit a bone. Weed,hemp,ganja
我和你在一起,切奇（《大麻》的主演）
I'm with you,Cheech.
-你认为他会冷静吗? -这里很干燥吗?
-Do you think he's gonna be cool? -ls it dry in here?
我来为你倒杯酒
Let me get you some wine.
我们可以上第一道菜了
I think we're ready for our first course too.
这些是石虾小方饺
These are rock shrimp ravioli in a cilantro ponzu sauce...
芫萎调味酱加上一点点…
...with just a touch of minced...
碎姜
...ginger.
打我屁股叫我朱蒂
Well,smack my ass and call me Judy!
-真是太好吃了 -我真高兴你喜欢
-These are fantastic! -Gosh! I'm so glad you liked them.
喜欢?我可以吃下上百个
Like them? I could eat 100 of them!
只有这一些
That's all there is of these...
但再过8分半钟 我们就会献上美味的洋葱馅饼
...but in a few minutes,we'll serve some tartlets.
馅饼...
"Tartlets"?
"Tartlets."
馅饼...
文字都已失去意义
Word has lost all meaning.
请问需要任何帮忙吗?
Excuse me. Can I help you with anything?
你看,我也不知道自己在找什么
You know,I don't know what I'm looking for.
酷,墨西哥馅饼
Cool! Taco shells!
这个就像是玉米卷
They're like a little corn envelope,you know?
-你不该影响食欲. -糖
-You don't wanna spoil your appetite. -Hey,Sugar-O's!
再等6分钟半
You know,if you just wait another 6 1 /2 minutes
干酪通心面!我们要做这个
Macaroni and cheese! We gotta make this!
-不,我们不做 -哦,好吧.
-No,we don't. -Oh,okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
我们何不坐这儿
Why don't you just have a seat here?
-小熊软糖给我 -不
-Give me the gummy bears. -No.
-把他给我 -好吧,分你一半
-Give them to me. -We'll share.
-小熊给我 -你不能全部抢走
-No. Give me the bears. -You can't have any.
这样不值得!
It's not worth it!
小熊落水了,他们快淹死了
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
不要站在那里.打9-1-1.
Don't just stand there. Call 9-1 -1.
嗨,伙计们,抓住糖逃命啊!
Hey,fellas,grab onto a Sugar-O! Save yourselves!
救命啊....我淹水了
Help! Help,I'm drowning!
-我受够了,晚餐结束 -什么?为什么?
-That's it! Dinner is over! -What! Why?
为什么?试想一下我到你的办公室然后开始...?
Why? What if I came into your office and I started...?
我想不出一个合适的例子.
I can't think of an example.
这机会我已等了七年
I've waited seven years for an opportunity like this...
而你却等不了四分半钟之后 再吃洋葱馅饼
...and you can't wait 4 1/2 minutes for a tartlet?
所以我跟他说,"对不起.这就是我的感受."
So I told him,"I'm sorry. That's how I feel."
他居然说我声音太刺耳搞得他耳朵嗡嗡叫
And he told me I harsh-ed his buzz.
然后我说,"别吃这个,这是厨房磁铁"
Then I said,"Don't eat that. It's a kitchen magnet."
结果他不听,我们只好把他留在急救室了.
And he didn't listen,so we left him in the emergency room.
-莫妮卡，很遗憾 -真是个王八蛋
-Mon,I'm sorry. -What a tool.
-你做的很对 -你不会想为那种人工作的
-You did the right thing. -You don't wanna work for that guy.
我以为我的机会来了
I just thought that this was it.
-不要担心.你是个了不起的厨师 -那些赞美的声音我不是装的
-Don't worry. You're an amazing chef. -Those yummy noises? I wasn't faking.
我能拿到全部三小时工资吗?
Am I gonna get paid for the full three hours?
只是一个问题而已.我们以后再说.
Just a question. We'll talk about it later.
和希莉亚的状况如何?
So,how did it go with Celia?
-简直是不可思议 -干得好,罗斯!
-I was unbelievable. -All right,Ross!
我就像是詹姆斯米切纳（历史学家）一样满口猥亵的话
I was the James Michener of dirty talk.
天下最具巧思的猥亵话
It was the most elaborate filth ever heard.
有人物,剧情,主题
I mean,there were characters,plot lines,themes,a motif.
其中一段的主角是村夫与村姑
At one point,there were villagers.
然后呢?
And?
猥亵话讲完后已经很晚了
By the time we finished all the dirty talk...
而且我们也已精疲力竭所以…
...it was late and we were exhausted
-你们爱抚? -那种感觉好好
-You cuddled. -Yeah,which was nice.
你们想看晚场电影吗?
Do you guys want to try to catch a late movie?
-或许吧,但我们不是该等钱德? -他到底跑哪儿去了?
-Shouldn't we wait for Chandler? -Where the hell is he?
我知道现在几点
I know what time it is...
但我看着WENUS而且我相当不高兴
...but I'm looking at the WENUS and I'm not happy!
真的?告诉你吧
Let me tell you something.
你会在乎是因为我在乎,明白了吗?很好!
You will care about it because I care about it. Got it? Good!
这样如何?
How's this?
不好意思,这边呢?
Sorry. How about over here?
这就说明有效果了.
That means it's working.
-痛不痛? -不痛.
-Does this hurt? -No.
这样呢?
How about this?
爽啦!
There you go!
我快吐了!
I'm gonna throw up!